# **RUSSELL SHEN**

**Phone:** (661) 917-5430

Email: shenzhaolin@gmail.com

Address: 5 Sailview, Newport Coast, CA 92657

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Nearly eight years of well-rounded experience working professionally in the financial industry. Driven, logical, and a fast learner with a depth understanding of financial data, able to perform various finance-related tasks and generate accurate forecasts.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

## Sep. 2017 - Present Newport Coast, CA

#### Trustee, Sunshine Irrevocable Trust

Perform research studies, develop investment plans based on risk tolerance and outlook expectations, host discussions with beneficiaries to present suitable targets, and invest accordingly.

## Apr. 2019 – Present Shanghai□Remote□, China

## Research Manager, Eureka Investment Partner Co.,Ltd.

Lead the execution of continuous research and due diligence on numerous public companies by directing methods, supervising junior analysts, and presenting findings to portfolio managers.

## Feb. 2017 - Dec. 2018 New York, NY

## **Equity Trader, T3 TRADING GROUP LLC**

Familiarized with technical indicators and performed high-frequency trading accordingly, achieved 48% ROI during the position duration.

## Nov. 2013 – May. 2015 Shanghai□Remote□, China

#### Financial Research Analyst, HUACHUANG SECURITIES BROKERAGE CO. LTD

Working closely with Mr. Zhao Qian-Ming (three times award winner for the best analyst in China in small-to-medium cap companies sector by CNI New Fortune Analyst Index) and Mr. Ba Shu-Song (Chief China Economist of Hong Kong Exchanges and Clearing Limited) to develop financial projections and assist in report publishing.

## **EDUCATION**

## May. 2017

#### Master of Science: Investor Relations

· Fordham University - New York, NY

## May. 2015

#### **Bachelor of Science: Finance**

· Saint Louis University - St. Louis, MO

#### CERTIFICATIONS

SQL for Data Science - University of California, Davis Credential ID: N9T6NKJL336

Python for Data Science, AI & Development - IBM Credential ID: VKXDBKGZNBW5